理查·基爾
戴安·蓮恩
奧立佛·馬丁內茲
《出軌》
外頭風好大
Pretty windy out.
千萬別是在打暴力電玩 當然不是，媽
- That better not be the violent one. - It's not, Mom.
爸，看我做的
Dad, look what I can do.
我練好久了
I've been practicing.
太出色了，小子 酷!
- Spectacular, kiddo. - Cool.
你衣服穿反了
You're inside out.
我知道 對你不管用吧？
I knew that. Doesn't work for you?
不敢相信你竟然教他那樣
I can't believe you taught him that.
我沒有，是他自己學的
I didn't. He did it on his own.
查理，你刷牙了沒？ 刷了
- Charlie, did you brush your teeth? - Yes.
查理! 我刷過了啦
- Charlie. - I brushed them.
你來看一下，康妮 我們走，我說認真的
- Look at this, Con. - Let's go. I'm serious.
你快把我給逼瘋了，媽
You're driving me bonkers, Mom.
還記得你說別買全谷股票嗎？
Remember when you said no to buying Omnidell?
記得那時價錢多少嗎？ 一股50元
- Remember what the price was? - One fifty.
很接近，是61元
Close. Sixty-one.
我自己來，媽 不，我幫你
- I'll do it, Mom. - No, I'll do it.
你知道現在行情多少了嗎？
You know what it's going for now?
說"一"! 一...
- Say "E. " - E.
猜猜看，康妮 愛德華，我不知道，好嗎？
- Guess, Con. - Edward, I don't know, all right?
現在漱口吧! 漲到74元了
- Now rinse. - Seventy-four.
真的漱口. 順便尿個尿
Really rinse. And pee.
74元! 早該買下來，可惡!
Seventy-four. Should have bought it. Shit.
那就買一點嘛! 太遲了，康絲，太遲了
- So buy some. - Too late, Con. Too late.
把蓋子掀起來，甜心
Lift the seat, honey.
別忘了放下馬桶蓋
Don't forget to put it down.
等你尿完的時候
When you finish.
你真的得帶這麼多東西嗎？
- Do you really need all that stuff? - Mom, no one wears these dorky hats.
媽，沒有人會戴這種唐老鴨帽啦!
你戴又不表示你是唐老鴨
- You do and you're not a dork. - How do I look?
我看來如何？
很帥
Very handsome.
我愛妳 好了，快點，要走了
Love you. Okay, come on, let's go.
快點
Come on.
你不應該出門的
You shouldn't go in.
我有些東西要在拍賣會上賣 而且他生日就快到了
I have stuff to do for the auction. And there's a birthday soon.
我要拉特媞腹P斯普雷威爾球衣，媽 別忘了
Latrell Sprewell jersey, Mom. Don't forget.
他是揚基隊的，對吧？ 媽，你快把我給逼瘋了
- He's on the Yankees, right? - Mom, you're driving me bonkers.
你快把他給逼瘋了
You're driving him bonkers.
天啊!
Jesus.
出租車! 可惡!
Taxi! Shit.
出租車!
Taxi!
真對不起
I'm so sorry.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我來幫妳撿東西
I'll get your things.
出租車! 出租車!
Taxi! Taxi!
我的書
My books.
你能幫我攔輛出租車嗎？ 好的
- Could you help me get a taxi? - Okay.
我會顧好你的書 謝謝
- I'll watch your books. - Thanks.
慘的連出租車都叫不到 都怪這陣可怕的風
- Bad day for taxis. - It's this horrible wind.
對，你像顆子彈被擊倒了!
Yeah, you shot down there like a bullet!
如果你揮動一下手臂 現在早就在家了
If you flapped your arms, you'd be home now.
下回我會記住的
I'll remember that next time.
情況不太妙 我知道
- That's not good. - I know.
聽著，我就住在樓上，有花盆那間
Listen, that's me up there. The flowerpot.
我幫你貼個繃帶，好嗎？
I'll get you a Band-Aid, okay?
抓緊一點，別被吹跑了
Hold onto something. Don't blow away.
還是你要上來清洗一下？
Or you can come on up and clean it off, no?
來吧!
Come on.
我又不是什麼連環殺手，我發誓
I'm not an ax murderer. I promise.
可惡!
Shit.
死電梯!
Fucking elevator.
再爬一層就到了
One more.
抱歉這媔礙澈 你是個作家？
- Pardon the mess. - Are you a writer?
我是個書商
I'm a book dealer.
浴室就在那堙A在左手邊
Bathroom's right down there, on the left.
去啊! 堶惘陪蚋暵鐃d
Go ahead. There's a medicine cabinet.
你可以偷瞄一下我的藥方
You can sneak a peek at my prescriptions.
哈囉？
Hello?
我替你泡了點茶 謝謝!
- I made you some tea. - Thank you.
你練拳擊？ 年輕時候有在練
- Do you box? - I used to, when I was young.
這地方真神奇
This is an amazing place.
沒錯，但這房子不是我的 不是？
- Yeah, but it's not mine. - No?
屋主是我朋友，他是雕刻家 現在人去了巴黎
The owner is a friend, a sculptor. He's in Paris.
真是酷! 我們可以住在這堙A我和我的書
That's cool. We can stay here, me and my books.
可以借個電話嗎？ 我得打個電話回家
Can I use your phone? I have to call home.
當然可以! 電話就在你後面
Sure, there's a phone just behind you.
謝謝
Thank you.
葛蘿莉亞？ 嗨，是我
Gloria? Hi, it's me.
好，很好. 查理怎樣？
Good, good. How's Charlie?
嗨，甜心! 今天在學校過的如何？
Hi, honey. How was your day at school?
真的？ 什麼部份最精彩呢？
Yeah? What was the best part?
你猜怎著？ 你相信嗎？ 媽咪錯過了班車
Guess what? Can you believe it? Mommy missed her train.
冰塊
Ice.
約一個小時
About an hour.
你該去做功課了
You should start your homework.
我保證見了面會一五一十地告訴你 我愛你，再見!
I promise to tell you all about it when I see you. I love you. Bye.
是我兒子查理 現在8歲，下周就9歲了
That was my son, Charlie. He's 8. He'll be 9 next week.
我叫保羅·馬提爾，我七月份就滿28歲了
I'm Paul Martel. I'll be 28 in July.
我叫康絲坦斯，我遲到了，我該走了
I'm Constance. And I'm late. I have to go.
你走之前，拿本書去看吧!
Before you go, take a book.
不，我不行
No. I couldn't.
當然可以，當作紀念品
Sure you can. A souvenir.
走到那邊. 你知道，跟之前一樣
Go down there. You know, like before.
好吧
Okay.
繼續走. 停!
Keep going. Stop.
現在找右邊
Now right.
不對，右邊
No, right.
好的，從上面數下來第二層書架...
Okay, now the second shelf from the top. . .
...左邊數來第四本
. . .take the fourth one from the left.
拿了嗎？
Got it?
拿了! 打開第23頁
- Think so. - Open to page 23.
品酒: 永恆的人生
Drink wine, this is life eternal
酒，讓你回復青春
This, all that youth will give to you
是美酒、玫瑰，把酒狂歡的季節
It is the season for wine, roses And drunken friends
要實時行樂
Be happy for this moment
此刻便是你的人生
This moment is your life
我得走了，謝謝
I have to go. Thank you.
你知道怎麼出去吧？ 但願如此
- Can you find your way out? - I hope so.
那是我的臥房
That's my bedroom.
很高興遇見你，康絲坦斯
It was nice meeting you, Constance.
如果你需要別的書或醫療就過來這
Come back if you need more books or medical attention.
嗨，葛蘿莉亞
Hey, Glo.
電視該關掉了，是吧？ 我正要關掉
- That wouldn't be the TV on, would it? - I was just turning it off.
想必如此
Sure you were.
風把我吹倒了 真的？
- The wind knocked me down. - Yeah?
你沒事吧？ 要不要給醫生看一下？
You all right? You need anything?
哇! 你和別人打架了嗎？ 不，只是跌倒而已
- Gross. Were you in a fight? - No, just fell over.
痛不痛？ 有一點
- Does it hurt? - Little bit.
酷! 你去哪堙H
- Cool! - Where are you going?
去拿相機! 試試這個
- To get the camera! - Try this.
你拿相機要做什麼？ 交學校作業用. 我們弄的血腥一點
- Why do you need the camera? - It's for school. We're doing blood.
好的，現在裝成真的很痛的樣子
Okay, now look like it really hurts.
準備好沒？ 好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
這一定很棒!
This will be great.
風把她吹倒，害的她流血了
The wind blew her down. She bled and everything.
每個人的帽子都被吹跑了 好個戰地攝影師. 你沒事吧？
- Everybody's hats blew off. - Quite the war photographer. You okay?
是的，風把我像個老太婆似的吹倒
Yeah. It took me down like an old lady.
真是丟臉! 爸! 來看看照片
- It was humiliating. - Dad, look at the pictures.
至少我們有了證據 可以告誰嗎？
At least we got the evidence. Anyone we can sue?
不能，有一個好心人幫忙我
No. There was this nice guy who helped me.
就像這樣，爸 是龍捲風
It was like this, Dad. It was a twister.
爸，你看，就像這樣
Dad, look. It was like this.
哇! 是龍捲風
- Wow. - It's a tornado.
他住在那兒附近. 他拿繃帶給我還幫我叫了部出租車
He lived around there. He got me some Band-Aids and put me in a taxi.
他長的帥嗎？
Was he good-looking?
我覺得不舒服
I feel sick.
你作業寫了沒？ 還沒，我不知道怎麼寫
- You do your homework? - I can't. I don't know how to do it.
快點，我來幫你 然後你再來幫我
Come on, I'll help you. Then you can help me with mine.
知道他的名字嗎？
Did you get his name, this guy?
我們可以送瓶酒給他
We could send him a bottle of wine.
便宜點的
Cheap wine.
康妮，站在那塈O動 等一下
Con, stand there a second. Wait a minute.
站在那堣@下 我正想辦法搞清楚這台....
Stay there a second. I'm trying to figure out the. . . .
我搞不懂焦距怎樣調整
The thing I can't figure out is the zoom-thing.
找到了 好的，等等，站在那
There it is. Okay, hold on, stay there.
把焦距拉近一點
Got the zoomy-thingy zooming.
待在那. 我正設法搞懂操作方法 我看看焦距有沒有對準
Stay there. I'm trying to figure this out. I wanna see if it focuses.
酷. 非常酷
Cool. Very cool.
真漂亮. 你自己也曉得
So beautiful. If you only knew.
看看你. 天啊，真是個美人
Look at you. God, what a beauty.
有事煩心嗎？
Something the matter?
沒事. 一點事也沒有
Nothing. Nothing at all.
這真的很棒 不，不好. 拿開
- This is really good. - No, it isn't. Go away.
我想我真的對焦了 我找到焦距了. 找到了
I think I'm really zooming. I found the zoom. Found it.
爸
Dad.
該死 媽
- Shit. - Mom.
我睡不著
I can't sleep.
我馬上回來. 我馬上回來 別睡著了
I'll be back. I'll be back. Don't fall asleep.
有用
It works.
媽，你秀逗了嗎？ 你忘了準備我的午餐
Mom, are you nuts? You forgot my lunch.
我沒忘. 就在門邊 跟我來
I did not. It's by the door. Come with me.
你在嚼什麼東西？ 沒什麼
- What are you chewing? - Nothing.
吐出來，那是什麼？
Spit that out. What is that?
真可愛 媽？
- That's lovely. - Mom?
我不想演只笨兔子
I don't want to be a dumb bunny.
甜心，演戲而已 還有其它很多兔子. 會很酷的
Honey, it's a play. There's lots of other bunnies. It'll be cool.
你瘋了，媽 那麼你告訴我
- You're bonkers, Mom. - So you tell me.
我愛你 我也愛你. 那是什麼？
- Love you. - Love you too. What's that?
謝謝
Thank you.
再見
Bye.
嗨，我是保羅·馬提爾 嗶聲後請留下你的訊息. 謝謝
Hi, this is Paul Martel. Leave a message after the beep. Thanks.
喂？ 喂？
Hello? Hello?
- Hello? - Hello?
你在哦
You're there.
我是康妮·桑納，狂風天碰到的那個人
This is Connie Sumner, the one from the windy day.
哦，那一個
Oh, that one.
膝蓋如何？ 你有冰敷嗎？
How's the knee? Did you ice it?
有的，我有冰敷且墊高腳 全照你說的去做
Yes, I iced it and I elevated it. You name it, I did it.
好多了 我只是想打個電話跟你道謝
It's much better. I just wanted to call and thank you.
我想問一下你的地址 因為我想要--
I wanted your address because I wanted...
你在哪堙H 你說什麼？
- Where are you? - What?
我說，你人在哪堙H
I said, where are you?
我在中央車站 真的聽不太清楚你的聲音
I'm in Grand Central. It's really hard to hear you.
過來看我 什麼？
- Come and see me. - What?
對，過來坐一下 我煮咖啡給你喝
Yeah, take a break. I'll make you some coffee.
咖啡？
Coffee?
好的! 好的!
- Okay. - Okay.
再見了
See you. Bye.
靠!
Fuck.
沒成了永久殘廢吧，跳給我看看
No permanent damage, I see.
政府有醫療補助、藍十字會... 我沒投保
- We take Medicaid, Blue Cross. . . . - I'm uninsured.
不行，恐怕我們無法接受慈善救濟
No. I'm afraid we don't take charity cases.
開個玩笑啦!
It was a joke.
看看這本. 傑克·倫敦著作
Look at this. Jack London.
"白牙"的初稿，還是原始書套
First edition of White Fang, in the original dust jacket.
我花一元五角買的
And I got it for a buck fifty.
現在值多少呢？ 大概超過4000倍以上價錢
- What's it worth? - About 4000 times more.
是用法文寫的 我在學校學過法文
- Those are in French. - I took it in school.
我要脫掉嗎？
Do I want to take off something?
你的外套. 要不要把外套脫下來？
Your coat. Would you like to take off your coat?
好的，我的外套
Yes, my coat.
謝謝
Thank you.
但我不能待太久 我還有些事要辦
But I can't stay very long. I have some errands I have to run.
我去沖咖啡 好的
- I'll get the coffee. - Okay.
那是點字書 點字
- It's in Braille. - Braille.
不，不，布萊爾 他是法國人
No, no, Braille. He was French.
閉上眼睛
Close your eyes.
什麼？ 閉上眼睛
- What? - Close your eyes.
「我母親為我燉了隻雞
My mother makes me chicken
吃了她的雞讓我咳嗽不已
Her chicken makes me cough
我希望她在燉的時候
I wish that when she made it
能把雞毛拔乾淨」
She took the feathers off
書上不是那麼寫的
It doesn't say that.
(烹飪之樂)
我最好走了 什麼？
- I had better go. - Yeah?
我最好走了
I'd better go.
小心，別跌倒了
Take care. Don't fall.
謝謝你的咖啡 你還沒喝呢
- Thanks for the coffee. - You didn't drink it.
林賽，嗨 康妮
- Lindsay, hi. - Connie.
我通知他一下 謝謝
- Let me buzz him. - Thanks.
嘿，真是意外. 看看你
Hey, what a surprise. Look at you.
嗨，比爾 嗨，康妮
- Hi, Bill. - Hi, Connie.
我打擾到你們嗎？ 不，我正要離開
- Am I interrupting? - No, I'm leaving.
我晚點拿預算案給你 好的，謝謝
- I'll get you the budget later. - All right, thanks.
要喝杯咖啡嗎？ 不用了，謝謝
- Would you like a coffee? - No, thank you.
太好了
That's nice.
我不知道你今天要來
I didn't know you were coming in today.
你冷死了 那是什麼？
You're freezing. What is that?
我在轉角附近，就幫你帶了件禮物
I was around the corner and I brought you a present.
哇. 是什麼特別日子嗎？
Wow. What's the occasion?
沒有. 我不知道
Nothing. I don't know.
是中碼的，但店員說會越穿越松
It's a medium, but they said it runs large.
看看那個 你不必現在穿上
- Look at that. - You don't have to try it on.
我是老闆，我高興怎樣就怎樣
I'm the boss. I can do whatever I want.
你覺得怎樣？
What do you think?
等我一下
Hold on just a second.
是的？
Yeah?
好的，其它電話暫時不接了
Okay, but hold the other calls.
你在忙，我先走了 坐一下
- You're busy. I'll go. - Sit.
我要走了 不，坐下
- I'll go. - No, sit.
你好，亨利？ 那到底是什麼問題停擺了？
Hello, Henry? So, what is this suspension problem?
不，我沒收到
No, I never received it.
好，送過來給我
Well, get it to me.
那還不夠好 我坐在這堿\等，200台卡車動彈不得
It's not good enough. I'm sitting here with 200 trucks I can't use.
好，安排個時間見面 我要法蘭克·博朋在場
Well, set up a meeting. And I want Frank Birnbaum there.
因為我交待別人辦事，就得辦好才成
Because when I tell someone to do something, I want it done.
我相信你會的
I'm sure you will.
你還得辦什麼事嗎？
So, what else you up to?
拍賣會 是嗎？ 你看中了誰？
- Auction. - Yeah? Who'd you hit on?
隨便猜猜
The usual suspects.
誰？
Who?
鮑伯·蓋洛德 鮑伯？
- Bob Gaylord. - Bob?
叫鮑伯做擔保 他們應該派你到中東去
Get Bob to pledge and they should send you to the Middle East.
說吧
So tell me.
什麼？
What?
你覺得怎樣？ 有像老闆吧
What do you think? It's a keeper.
哈囉 哈囉
- Hello. - Hello.
我又來了. 我帶了些鬆餅
Here I am again. I brought muffins.
這首是什麼音樂？ 你喜歡嗎？
- What is this music? - Do you like it?
是的
Yes.
想跳支舞嗎？
Do you want to dance?
現在？ 是的
- Now? - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
我必須警告你，由我來帶舞 當然，你是美國人
- I have to warn you, I tend to lead. - Of course. You are American.
你以前跳過？ 什麼？
- You've done this before. - What?
你交過幾個女朋友？
How many girlfriends have you had?
兩個
Two.
真的？ 我會騙你嗎？
- Really? - Would I lie to you?
不知道. 你會嗎？
I don't know. Would you?
你的眼睛真漂亮，你應該連晚上都別閉上
Your eyes are amazing. You should never shut them, not even at night.
你應學會張著眼睛睡覺
You should learn to sleep with your eyes open.
我可以辦的到 你能嗎？ 〔歌聲〕你能能能.....
- I'll work on that. - Will you?
等一下
Hang on.
我想這是錯誤的
I think this is a mistake.
根本沒有錯誤，全看你願不願意而已
There are no mistakes. There's what you do, and what you don't do.
我不能這樣
I can't do this.
我忘了外套
Forgot my coat.
不行 怎麼？
- I can't. - What?
怎麼回事？
What's wrong?
我不知道怎麼辦 這是不對的
I don't know how to do this. It's wrong.
打我 什麼？
- Hit me. - What?
打我
Hit me.
嗨，愛德華 嗨，鮑伯
- Hey, Ed. - Hey, Bob.
好一陣子沒看到你了 沒錯
- Haven't seen you in a while. - No.
這禮拜我一直工作到很晚 真的？ 孩子怎麼樣？
- I've been working late this week. - Really? How's the boy?
他的生日到了 幾歲了？
- It's his birthday. - How old?
9歲
Nine.
那要不要全副武裝來個大搶劫？
So any major armed robberies?
不. 不，這禮拜不行
No. No, not this week.
說到這點，多注意一下康妮
Speaking of which, watch out for Connie.
她會叫你在你的抵押單據上簽名 什麼？
- She'll have you sign over your mortgage. - What?
她有設法說服你捐款嗎？ 沒有
- Did she try to hit on you for money? - No.
我以為她跟你提過 關於學校拍賣會的事，或者別的
I thought she talked to you about this school auction, or whatever.
沒跟我提過
Not me.
我一直出差在外 也許她跟瑪吉說過
I've been out of town. Maybe she talked to Maggie.
是的，我想是我搞錯了
Yeah, I guess I got it wrong.
總之，我們欠你一頓飯
Anyway, we owe you a dinner.
沒錯
Yeah.
他不在
He's out.
要不要帶東西給你？
Can I get you anything?
不. 不，我很好，謝謝
No. No, I'm fine, thanks.
今天辛苦了？ 不，不太會
- Tough day? - No, not really.
你呢？ 你今天過的如何？
What about you? How was your day?
很好
It was good.
你知道，就平常那些瑣事
You know, the usual stuff.
你確定不要點什麼嗎？
Sure you don't want anything?
不用
No.
康妮？ 什麼事？
- Con? - Yeah?
你愛我嗎？
Do you love me?
我當然愛你
Of course I love you.
真是個傻問題
What a silly question.
我猜...
I guess. . .
...我是覺得我有點傻
. . .I'm just feeling silly.
我馬上上去
I'll be up in a minute.
好的
Okay.
哦，抱歉
Oh, sorry.
你來這堸竣偵礡H
What are we doing here?
吃午餐啊!
Having lunch.
我不應該這樣 你不應該吃午餐嗎？
- I shouldn't be doing this. - You shouldn't have lunch?
不是跟你
Not with you.
我想我們應該離開
I think we should leave.
聽著
Listen.
看到那邊正要買單的人沒？
See those guys over there paying the check?
看到了 好的. 如果是右邊的人付錢...
- Yes. - Okay. If the guy on the right pays. . .
...我們馬上離開 如果是左邊的人付錢的話...
. . .we leave right now. If the guy on the left pays. . .
...我們就留下來
. . .we stay.
而且我要吻你
And I kiss you.
不
No.
賬單給我
Give me that.
我贏了
I win.
不 這就是生活
- No. - C'est la vie.
別那樣. 不要
Don't do it. Don't.
雙人房？ 當然
- Room for two? - Of course.
音樂很好聽. 是什麼音樂？
Nice music. What is it?
是...
It's. . .
...我想是非洲音樂吧
. . .African, I think.
我喜歡
I like it.
拿去
Here.
我們回房吧
Let's go to bed.
快點 在這堻郁
- Come on. - Stay here with me.
我好冷 留下來
- I'm cold. - Stay.
留在這堻郁 我好冷
- Stay here with me. - I'm cold.
我們走
Let's go.
中午一塊用餐如何？
How about lunch today?
你有空嗎？
You free?
我有一大堆募捐者的物品 得挑出要拍賣的
I have all this fundraiser stuff. Auction things to pick up.
要是你方便的話，我們可以提早一點 中午12點怎麼樣？
We can do an early one if you want. How about 12:00?
12點？
12:00?
是的
Yeah.
12點時不曉得會不會餓？
Will I be hungry at 12:00?
我們可以一塊進去用餐
We could go in together.
我會等你
I'll wait for you.
我還要一個鐘頭才有空 沒關係，我等你
- I won't be ready for another hour. - That's all right. I'll wait.
哦，該死 怎麼了？
- Oh, shit. - What?
我剛剛想起...
I just remembered. . .
我今天12點半要到喬琪安娜店堸筋容
. . .I have a facial at 12:30 at Georgianna's today.
哦，好的
Oh, well.
你得保持漂亮點，好嗎？
You gotta stay beautiful, right?
喬琪安娜美容院，是吧？
Georgianna's, huh?
浪費錢
Waste of money.
對，在曼哈頓
Yeah, Manhattan.
美容院稱作喬琪娜
A beauty salon called Georgina.
哦，是的，沒錯. 是的，喬琪安娜 沒錯
Oh, yeah, right. Yes, Georgianna's. That's right.
謝謝
Thank you.
你好，我想確認一下今天12點半的預約
Hello, I'm calling to confirm an appointment today at 12:30.
桑納. 康妮·桑納
Sumner. Connie Sumner.
S-U-M-N-E-R.
她會不會是改了預約時間？
Could she be down for another time?
不客氣，謝謝
No, thank you.
康妮？ 是康妮
Connie? It's Connie.
康妮？
Connie?
特蕾西？
Tracy?
嗨. 我正想打電話給你 電話老是...
- Hi. I was gonna call you. - They all say that. . .
...我打電話談兔子裝的事 見過家庭計劃中心的莎莉
. . .when I call about bunny costumes. You know Sally from Planned Parenthood.
嗨，好久不見 好久了
- Hi. It's been a while. - Too long.
你保養的真好 你要去哪？
- You look amazing. - So where you headed?
我正要去挑些廚房用的窗簾
I was going to look for some window shades for the kitchen.
我們要去喝咖啡 你何不跟我們一塊去？
We're gonna go and have coffee. Why don't you join us?
哦，我快遲到了 買窗簾會遲到？
- Oh, I'm gonna be late. - For window shades?
少來了 好吧
- Come on. - Okay.
嗨，你好嗎？
Hi, how are you?
我要去打個電話
I'm just gonna make a phone call.
好的 拿我的手機去打
- Sure. - Let me get that for you.
她可以用我手機打就好了呀 你說的對
- She could've used my cell phone. - Oh, you're right.
嗨，是我
Hi, it's me.
說起來你可能不信 我人在轉角的咖啡廳
You won't believe this. I'm at that cafe around the corner.
你幹嘛介紹我是家庭計劃中心的莎莉？
Why do you introduce me as Sally from Planned Parenthood?
聽起來好像我在推銷保險套似的
It makes it sound like I'm handing out condoms.
我被困在這堣F
I'm stuck here.
等我好嗎？
Will you wait for me?
等我!
Wait for me.
我打電話提醒葛蘿莉亞 去拿送洗的衣服
I called Gloria to remind her to pick up the dry cleaning.
查理真是人見人愛
Charlie is so adorable.
謝謝
Thank you.
我吃不下
I can't eat.
我要一杯咖啡 我想我也來杯咖啡好了
- I'll have a coffee. - Well, I guess I'll have coffee too.
再失陪一下，我上個洗手間
Excuse me again. Ladies' room.
天啊，她看起來氣色真好
God, she looks good.
你想她有去做整容嗎？ 她何必整容？ 她還耀眼的很
- You think she's had work? - Why would she? She's still gorgeous.
趁現在早點做，免得到時成了黃臉婆
They do it early now before it goes to shit.
我朋友在外面
I have friends out there.
你帶我來這最棒的地方
You take me to the best places.
我來
Let me.
她不像你說的那樣. 她真的很漂亮 當然漂亮了
- She's not like that. She's really nice. - Of course she is.
所以才更糟糕 她既漂亮又溫柔
That makes it worse. She's nice and she's sweet.
她的臀部跟在大學時一樣玲瓏有致
And her ass is in exactly the same place it was in college.
你有在打網球嗎？
Are you taking tennis?
哦，我可不會稱那回事為"打網球"
Oh, I wouldn't call what I do "taking tennis. "
你回來了. 我正開始要擔心你呢 不，我很好
- There you are. I was starting to worry. - No, I'm fine.
我們還以為你被帥哥給綁架了呢
We thought that heartthrob abducted you.
什麼帥哥啊？
What heartthrob?
你沒看到櫃檯那個男的嗎？ 好帥哦
You didn't see him at the counter? He was gorgeous.
我沒聽懂 你的扣子沒扣好
- I miss everything. - Your button's undone.
哦，謝謝
Oh. Thank you.
就是他
That's him.
我看他對我有意思
I can see the appeal.
如果他看我兩次 我馬上轉頭過去
If he looked at me twice, I'd be on my back.
你不會的 我會的. 為何說不會？
- You would not. - I would so. Why not?
兩項理由: 亞當和你的孩子
A couple of reasons: Adam and your kids.
你知道，特蕾西，不必給他們知道
You know, Trace, they wouldn't have to know.
這很可能是我自己跨越禁忌尺度
It could be something I did for myself, to broaden my horizons.
就像上陶藝班一樣
Like taking a pottery class.
戀愛又不像上陶藝班 有可能
- An affair isn't like taking pottery. - Could be.
戀情會像那樣開始發展出來 然後就發生了關係...
It would start out like that. Then something would happen. . .
被人發現有了外遇 最後結局都很慘
. . .someone finds out or someone falls in love and it ends disastrously.
總是以悲劇收場
They always end disastrously.
不
No.
什麼時候？
When?
很久以前了
It was a long time ago.
如果可能的話，我希望能重來一遍
And it's the one thing in my life I would undo if I could.
你越過街道就只是為了干我？
Did you just fuck me across the street?
是的
I did.
我們可以立刻結束這段關係 誰也不會受到傷害
We could end this now and no one would get hurt.
是的. 我想如果現在結束的話 我會受到傷害
Yeah. I think if we ended this now, I'd get hurt.
所以不管怎樣，有人會受到傷害？ 也許不會
- So no matter what, someone gets hurt? - Maybe not.
也許我們會彼此厭倦對方
Maybe we'll get tired of each other.
天啊，真希望我能厭倦你
God, I hope I get tired of you.
你深植我心坎底
You're in my mind.
每早醒來第一個想到的就是你
You're the only thing in my mind when I wake up every morning.
還沒張眼之前，你就浮現在我腦海了
You're in my brain before I even open my eyes.
你想的是什麼？ 不一定
- What do you think of? - That depends.
如果哪一天不知能否見到你時 我會很緊張...
If it's a day when I don't know if I'm gonna get to see you, I'm anxious. . .
...想盡借口來這堿搷A
. . .thinking of excuses to come to the city to see you.
你知道我們要見面的日子嗎？
And the days you know we'll meet?
每逢那些日子...
On those days. . .
...我...
. . .I'm. . .
平靜多了，也痛恨我自己
. . .calm and hating myself.
這堨u有這個
This is what we have over here.
我下午就幫你準備好了
I'll have it ready for you this afternoon.
愛德華，怎麼了？ 聽起來很重要的樣子
Ed, what's up? Sounded important.
我聽說你跟鄧巴、布爾克 及其它公司洽談
I've heard you're talking with Dunbar and Brinks and other companies.
你從哪媗巨茠滿H
Where did you hear that?
嗯，聽著
Well, look.
我想他們可能是要挖角我過去 若你的意思是那樣
I suppose they could be wooing me, if that's what you mean.
很明顯地一堆人要挖你跳槽 還是誰在挖誰呢？
Apparently a lot of people are wooing you. Or who's wooing who?
你在說什麼呀？ 我跟一些人談過了
What are you talking about? So I talked to some people.
那又怎樣？ 這是關於忠誠，比爾
- So what? - This is about loyalty, Bill.
我讓你走 要是有需要的話我可以寫推薦函
I'm letting you go. You'll have my recommendation if you need it.
我有一家人要養活，愛德華
I have a family, Ed.
你這堣]有一家人
You had a family here.
不，等一等 你跟我談論家人？
No, wait a minute. You're telling me about family?
最重要的事你都被蒙在鼓
You don't know the first goddamn thing about it.
注意你自己該死的家人，愛德華
Look at your own fucking family, Ed.
他媽的注意一下!
Take a goddamn look at that.
愛德華 法蘭克
- Ed. - Frank.
謝謝你這麼快趕來
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
這是私事，與公事無關
This is personal, it's not business.
考慮一下 你可能不願意牽扯到這件事
Think about it. You might not want to get involved.
但我需要找個信得過的人
But I need someone I can trust.
我要你跟蹤一個人
I want you to follow somebody.
我要你跟蹤我老婆
I want you to follow my wife.
著火了，媽 什麼？
- It's burning, Mom. - What?
著火了. 雞肉
It's burning. The chicken.
可惡
Shit.
水滾了，媽. 水滾開了!
It's boiling, Mom. It's boiling!
謝謝
Thank you.
小心! 小心!...
Watch it. Watch it.
抱歉，雞肉有點燒焦
Chicken's a little dry. I'm sorry.
沒關係
It's fine.
我明天要去芝加哥
I have to go to Chicago tomorrow.
去多久？ 不會很久. 可能只住一個晚上
- For how long? - Not long. Probably just a night.
幾點的班機？
What time's your flight?
八點
Eight o'clock.
早上？
A.M.?
戴安·德萊厄爾的兒子跟艾美·琳恩的女兒 要結婚
Dianne Dreyer's son is marrying Amy Lynn's daughter.
我絕不要結婚 為什麼不要？
- I'm never getting married. - Why not?
我討厭女孩子
I hate girls.
你以後就會改變心意的
You might change your mind. That happens sometimes.
我才不會
I won't.
什麼？ 我今天將比爾·史東解雇了
- What? - I fired Bill Stone today.
你是在煩那件事嗎？ 我沒在煩
- That's what's bothering you? - Nothing's bothering me.
你為什麼要解雇他？
Why did you fire him?
他不夠負責 什麼是負責？
- He's not accountable. - What's accountable?
是不是像人吃人？ 不是
- Isn't it like people who eat people? - No.
那是食人族，甜心
That's a cannibal, honey.
總之，我再也信不過他了
Anyway, I can't trust him anymore.
所以如果你碰到桃莉，你就會明白
So if you run into Dolly, you'll know.
怎麼？ 沒想到你這樣!
- What? - I can't believe you!
我做了什麼？
What did I do?
糟糕!
Shit!
快點!
Come on!
真對不起. 真的很對不起
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
甜心，你沒事吧？
Honey, you okay?
你一定非常擔心 住手，媽. 別人會看到
- You must have been so worried. - Stop, Mom. People can see.
嗨，我是保羅·馬提爾 嗶聲後請留下您的訊息
Hi, this is Paul Martel. Leave a message after the beep.
媽？
Mom?
你應該上床睡覺了
You're supposed to be in bed.
你在哭，媽 哦，甜心
- You're crying, Mom. - Oh, honey.
媽咪只是有點難過而已 來吧，我帶你回房睡覺
Mommy's just a little sad, that's all. Come on, I'll take you bed.
我帶你去睡覺
Let's get you into bed.
別難過了，媽 爸明天就回家了
Don't be sad, Mom. Dad will be home tomorrow.
他叫保羅·馬提爾
His name is Paul Martel.
住在梅瑟街433號，3號公寓
He lives at 433 Mercer Street, Apartment 3.
她白天時候去找他
She sees him during the day.
通常都在午餐時間前後
Usually goes around lunchtime.
約逗留個兩、三小時
Stays about two hours, maybe three.
他們去電影院？
They go to the movies?
那天有去 除此之外，還去了他家
They did that day. Otherwise, they're in his place.
快點接!
Pick up.
嘿，小姐!
Hey, lady!
你鑰匙忘了給
Forgot your keys.
等等!
Wait!
她是誰？ 她是誰？
Who is she? Who is she?
冷靜點! 你在幹什麼？
Calm down! What are you doing?
還有幾個？ 5個、10個？
How many are there? Five, ten?
我算什麼，星期一那一個？ 我弄錯日子了嗎？
What am I, the Monday one? Did I get my day wrong?
她只是個朋友，好嗎？ 只是朋友
She's just a friend, okay? Just a friend.
你這該死的騙子 我？ 我是騙子？
- You're a fucking liar. - Me? I'm the liar?
我不會再跟你來往了
I can't do this anymore.
那好. 回去你的郊區和車庫 打你的網球--
Fine. Go back to your suburb and car pool, your tennis...
你在做什麼？
What are you doing?
操你 會教你很爽的
- Fuck you. - That'll make you happy.
去你的
Fuck you.
不，不行
No, I can't.
保羅，結束了
Paul, it's over.
不行
I can't.
我恨你. 我恨你 我知道
- I hate you. I hate you. - I know.
住手，我不行
Stop it, I can't.
你要干我嗎？ 你要我幹嗎？
- Are you gonna fuck me? - You want me to?
我要 說出來
- I want you to. - Say it.
我要你干我 說出來
- I want you to fuck me. - Say it.
我要你干我
I want you to fuck me.
謝謝. 非常謝謝你
Thank you. Thank you very much.
真的很謝謝你
Thank you very much, indeed.
什麼事？
Yes?
你是保羅·馬提爾？ 是的
- You're Paul Martel? - Yes.
你多大年紀？
How old are you?
你是誰？
Who are you?
愛德華·桑納
Edward Sumner.
康妮的丈夫
Connie's husband.
我可以...？
May I. . .?
我可以進去嗎？
May I come in?
當然可以
Yeah. Sure.
你想喝點什麼嗎？ 好的
- Would you like a drink? - Yeah, why not?
我有威士忌、伏特加、柳橙汁....
I have Scotch, vodka, orange juice. . . .
伏特加
Vodka.
冰的嗎？
Is it cold?
是的
Yeah.
我放在冰箱媕Y
I keep it in the freezer.
我家堣]是
So do I, at home.
那麼告訴我，你是怎麼...
So tell me, how did you. . .
...認識我老婆的？
. . .meet my wife?
意外
By accident.
在街上. 那時颳大風，她的膝蓋受傷....
On the street. There was a windstorm, she hurt her knee and. . . .
你就是他
You're him.
她跟你說的？
She told you about that?
對
Yes.
你還好吧？
How's it going?
很好，很好. 我是指我沒事
Fine. Fine. I mean, okay.
你們在此幽會？ 是的
- This is where you meet? - Yes.
她喜歡嗎？ 我猜是的. 她沒抱怨過
- She likes it? - I guess. She never complained.
你們都一直待在這堙A或者也照樣外出？
Do you stay in all the time, or do you go out too?
看情況. 有時候會出門
It depends. Sometimes we go out.
那她喜歡出門嗎？
And she likes that?
她喜歡這附近？
She likes this neighborhood?
我想比住在郊區還刺激
More exciting than the suburbs, I guess.
你知道我們已經結婚11年了嗎？
Do you know we have been married 11 years?
我們有個兒子
We have a son.
她告訴過我
She told me.
還要嗎？
More?
好的，謝謝
Yes, please.
他就是我們搬離這城市的原因
He's the reason that we left the city.
康妮認為對他比較好
Connie thought it'd be better for him.
她說是你的主意
She told me it was your idea.
你們...談論我？
You talk about me?
好多書
A lot of books.
作些買賣
A lot of buying and selling.
我不知道能那樣
I didn't know it did that.
你怎麼有這個？ 是個禮物
- Where did you get this? - It was a gift.
她送的？
From her.
她為什麼要送你？ 不知道
- Why would she do that? - I don't know.
也許她只是想買點東西送我
Maybe she just wanted to buy me something.
這不是她買給你的 是我送她的
She didn't buy this for you. I gave it to her.
我受不了 怎麼了？
- I can't do this. - What?
我受不了. 我受不了
I can't do this. I can't do this.
我覺得不舒服. 我不行--
I'm feeling sick. I can't...
要喝點水嗎？
You want some water?
我覺得不舒服. 我--
I'm feeling sick. I'm...
我覺得--
I feel...
不舒服. 我覺得不舒服
I'm not well. I'm not feeling well.
我不是--
I'm not...
我覺得不--
I'm not feeling...
天啊!
God!
你不能死
You can't die.
嗨，我是保羅·馬提爾 嗶聲後請留下您的訊息
Hi, this is Paul Martel. Leave a message after the beep.
嗨，是我
Hi, it's me.
聽著
Listen.
這件事我不想對著錄音機說...
I don't like saying this to your machine...
...但我必須結束這段關係
...but I have to end this.
只是我...我不能再這樣下去了
I just... I can't do it anymore.
我不能這樣子生活下去
I can't live like this.
我厭倦了欺騙及傷害我的家人
I'm so tired of lying and hurting my family.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我希望....
And I hope...
我不知道我希望怎樣
I don't know what I hope.
對不起
I'm sorry.
訊息已刪除
Messages erased.
緊張嗎？
Does that pinch?
不會
No.
你知道你獨唱的部份嗎？ 知道
- Do you know your solo? - Yep.
我可以聽吧？
Can I hear it?
需要幫忙嗎？ 不用，我很好
- Need a hand? - No, I'm fine.
謝了
Thanks.
你去哪了？
Where were you?
沒事吧？
You okay?
你知道你很出色嗎？
You were spectacular, you know that?
他是不是很棒？ 是很棒
- Wasn't he great? - Great.
他太棒了，很棒
He was great. Great.
真的很棒
Really great.
我得幫忙打掃 回家後再給晚安吻，好嗎？
I have to help clean up. I'll kiss you good night when I get home, okay?
抱歉，愛德華. 好像是我把你綁死了 沒關係
- Sorry, Ed. Looks like I nailed you. - It's all right.
沒關係，傑瑞
It's all right, Jerry.
你最好檢查看看這打不打的開
You better check to see if this will open.
沒什麼. 車子很好
It's nothing. This is fine.
車有撞凹嗎，爸？ 是的
- Did he dent you, Dad? - Yes, he did. Yes.
要叫警察來嗎，爸？
Can we call the cops, Dad?
我們檢查一下後車廂 我們明天再談
- Let's check the trunk. - We'll talk tomorrow.
一下子就好了 不!
- It'll just take a second. - No!
哦，我的媽呀
Oh, my God.
查理，瞧瞧你爸，告訴他哪堣ㄨ麉l
Charlie, look at your dad and tell me what's wrong.
怎麼了？
What?
他的鞋子! 兩隻鞋子顏色不一樣
His shoes. They're different colors.
甜心，你看來糟透了
Honey, you look awful.
昨晚怎麼回事？ 你有睡嗎？ 我起床後找不到你
What happened last night? Did you sleep? I got up and looked for you.
我只是...
I just. . .
...去透個氣
. . .got some air.
你還好吧？
Are you okay?
很好
Yeah.
搬到這塈A喜歡嗎？
Do you like it here?
什麼？ 我當然喜歡這
What? Of course I like it here.
我們不一定得住在這 我們可以搬回城市住
We don't have to stay here. We can move back to the city.
甜心，你有何心事？
Honey, what has gotten into you?
你沒事吧？
Are you okay?
是的，沒事. 我很好
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine. Fine.
你還好吧？ 我很好
- Are you okay? - I'm fine.
大家都很好 我們哪堣]別搬
Everybody's fine. And we're not moving anywhere.
警察來了，媽
The cops are here, Mom.
他們來幹什麼？ 應該沒什麼
- What do they want? - I'm sure it's nothing.
紐約警探，媽
N.Y.P.D., Mom.
桑納太太？ 我是狄恩警探 這位是米羅尼克警探，紐約警探
Mrs. Sumner? I'm Detective Dean, this is Detective Mirojnick, N.Y.P.D.
有什麼事嗎？ 怎麼了？
Something happen? Is something wrong?
你認識保羅·馬提爾嗎？
Do you know a Paul Martel?
是的，不太熟. 怎麼？ 你知道他在哪嗎？
- Yes, not very well. Why? - Do you know where he is?
不知道
No.
我想在家吧
At home, I would imagine.
你知道他住哪嗎？
Do you know where he lives?
蘇活區，是不是？
SoHo, isn't it?
在他桌上找到你的名字和電話號碼
Your name and number were found on his desk.
他做了什麼壞事嗎？ 不清楚
- Has he done something wrong? - We don't know.
他的家人報案說他失蹤了
He's been reported missing by his family.
他老婆不知道他現在人在哪
His wife doesn't know where he is.
我不知道他結過婚了
I didn't know he was married.
分居了
Separated.
你上回見到他是什麼時候？
When did you see him last?
不記得了，很難說
I don't know, it's hard to say.
他是個書商
He's a book dealer.
不太認識 我之前要跟他買書
I barely know him. I was going to buy books from him.
買了嗎？ 不，還沒
- And did you? - No, not yet.
發生什麼事了嗎？ 你認為他沒事吧？
Has something happened? You think he's all right?
一時還很難說
It's hard to say at this point.
我們正在調查
We're working on it.
總之，謝謝. 謝謝你抽空回答 謝謝
- Anyway, thanks. Thanks for your time. - Thank you.
我喜歡這種玻璃雪花的玩意 我兒子就有一些
I like these snow-glass things. My boy has some of these.
如果有他消息的話，麻煩通知我們 沒問題
- If you hear from him, let us know. - Certainly.
爸! 警察今天來我們家
Dad! Cops came to our house today.
警察？ 他們來做什麼？
Cops? What did they want?
有人失蹤了
Someone's missing.
他們必須詢問每個人，你知道的
And they have to check everyone, you know.
誰失蹤了？
Who was it?
甜心，坐好
Honey, sit up straight.
誰失蹤了？ 我想你不認識他
- Who was it? - I don't think you know him.
是個賣書的
He sells books.
我忘了在哪見過他
I forget where I met him.
他是個壞蛋嗎，媽？
Was it a bad guy, Mom?
警察為什麼要給你問話？
Why did they want to talk to you?
我猜他有我的名字和電話號碼
I guess he had my name and number.
他為何會有你的電話號碼？
Why would he have your number?
我想是跟他買過書的關係
I think I bought a book from him.
小心點. 慢慢來 嘿，查理!
- Be careful. Take it easy. - Hey, Charlie!
哦，親愛的 哦，我希望你住近一點
Oh, my darling. Oh, I wished you lived closer.
主啊，感謝您賜給我們食物 以及您的恩寵
Lord, bless this food to our use, and us to thy service.
提醒我們去幫助別人，阿門
And help us be ever mindful of the needs of others. Amen.
阿門
Amen.
很好，愛德華
Very nice, Edward.
好了!
All right!
我說個你們不知道的愛德華的事 靠過來一點
I have a story you don't know about Edward. Gather close.
你好，桑納太太
Hello, Mrs. Sumner.
很抱歉週末還來打擾你們 我是狄恩警探
Sorry to bother you on the weekend. I'm Detective Dean.
這位是米羅尼克警探，紐約警探 好的
- This is Detective Mirojnick, N.Y.P.D. - Okay.
我們希望能跟你談個幾分鐘
We were hoping to talk to you for a few minutes.
沒問題
Sure.
查理，我們上去走廊那邊一下 我可以過去嗎？
- Charlie, we're going up on the porch. - Can I come?
不行，甜心. 待在外面 跟波比玩一下，我們馬上回來
No, sweetheart. Stay out here. Play with Poppy, we'll be right back.
不知道您老婆有沒有提過 上星期我們有來過
I don't know if your wife mentioned, we were here a week ago.
調查保羅·馬提爾的事
About Paul Martel.
有的，失蹤了的人
Yeah, the man who was missing.
嗯，他不會再失蹤了 屍體上週末被人發現了
Well, he's not missing anymore. His body was discovered last weekend.
天啊，太可怕了
God, that's terrible.
哦，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你想起來在哪見到馬提爾先生了嗎 桑納太太？
Do you recall where you met Mr. Martel, Mrs. Sumner?
我說過了 不，夫人，你沒說過
- I told you. - No, ma'am, you didn't.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我想不起來
I can't remember.
我想大概是募捐者吧
A fundraiser, I think.
你能說的更詳細點嗎？
Can you be more specific?
茱利亞德
Juilliard.
茱利亞德？
Juilliard?
音樂學校
The music school.
是的，我知道茱利亞德是什麼 你當然知道. 抱歉
- Yes, I know what Juilliard is. - Of course you do. I'm sorry.
你也去過嗎，先生？
Were you there too, sir?
是的. 是的，我想我去過
Yes. Yes, I think I was.
嗯，也許你見過馬提爾先生
Well, maybe you met Mr. Martel.
不. 不，就我記得沒見過
No. No, not that I remember.
也許你會認得他
Maybe you'd recognize him.
不，我從沒見過他
No, I've never met him before.
是他嗎？ 是的. 是的
- Is that him? - Yes. Yes.
你曾到過他的公寓？
You ever been to his apartment?
沒有
No.
沒有，我幾乎不認識他
No, I hardly knew him.
我不知道他為何會有我的電話號碼 也許他喜歡你
- I didn't know why he had my number. - Maybe he liked you.
聽著，夠了
Look, that's enough.
所以你從未到過他的公寓 那附近地區呢？
So you've never been to his apartment. How about the neighborhood?
逛過那媔隉H 沒有
- Hang out down there? - No.
不，不常...
No, not often. . .
...還是不，從來沒有
. . .or no, never.
從來沒有 我不記得上回到蘇活區是什麼時候了
Never. I can't remember the last time I was in SoHo.
事實上是四個星期前
It was four weeks ago, actually.
你有一張馬提爾公寓前的停車券 上面日期是四星期前
You got a parking ticket in front of Martel's apartment, four weeks ago.
哦，那個. 對，我跟朋友在一間小店喝咖啡
Oh, that. Right. I had coffee with friends at a little place.
我忘了
I forgot.
是特蕾西和莎莉 哦，是的. 是的. 對
- It was Tracy and Sally. - Oh, yeah. Yes. Yep.
聽好...
Look. . .
我老婆知道的全告訴你了，我也是
. . .my wife has told you everything she knows, so have I.
不介意的話，我去找我兒子
If you don't mind, we'd like to get back to our son.
好啦
All right.
我怎麼忘了給你我的名片呢？ 我有你的名片
- Why don't I give you my card? - I have your card.
對啊
Right.
祝你們週末愉快 你們也是
- Enjoy your weekend. - You too.
桑納，拜託
Sumner, please.
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
康妮？
Connie?
嗨，特蕾西
Hi, Tracy.
我只是來拿我今晚要穿的絲質套裝
I'm just picking up my silk suit for tonight.
我想穿這件黑色的
I was thinking of wearing the black.
我捐給了古德威 換別人好好亮相一番
I'm giving it to Goodwill. Let someone else be gorgeous for a change.
估且不談我們明亮的個性 我們該帶什麼過去？
What should we bring, aside from our sparkling personalities?
我們準備得如何了？ 很好
- How we doing? - Fine.
要幫手嗎？ 不用
- Need help? - No.
白酒不冰了 所以我把它放到進冰箱
Well, the white is not cold, so I'm gonna put it in the freezer.
記得提醒我放在堶情A好嗎？
Just remind me it's in there, all right?
大部份的人喜歡喝紅酒
Most people drink red anyway.
我喜歡這些小玩意 還有什麼地方你們沒去過？
I love these things. Is there any place you guys haven't been?
羅森索家有795個呢
The Rosenthals got 795 for their place.
短短兩天就接獲六張訂單 他們正在從事招標
- In two days they had six offers. - Sealed bids is how they do it now.
你覺得這間房子值多少，愛德華？
What do you think this place is worth, Ed?
不清楚. 如果賣了房子，要搬去哪？
I don't know. If you sell your house, where do you go?
以那些價錢，大溪地 曼谷
- At those prices, Tahiti. - Bangkok.
康妮，這個是哪來的？
Connie, where is this one from?
斐濟
Fiji.
記住，傑夫 我要你帶我去斐濟
Remember, Jeff, I asked you to take me to Fiji.
然後再帶我去夏威夷 每天悠閒地釣釣魚....
And then you took me to Hawaii. We went fishing every single. . . .
怎麼了，愛德華？
What happened, Edward?
你幹了什麼事？
What did you do?
是你傷害他的嗎？
Did you hurt him?
愛德華？
Edward?
是你傷害他的嗎？
Did you hurt him?
你做的，是不是？
You did, didn't you?
天啊，愛德華
Jesus, Edward.
說話呀
Talk to me.
告訴我你做了什麼!
Tell me what you did!
不，你告訴我你做了什麼
No, you tell me what you did.
你是如何一而再三地和他上床 還敢騙我!
How you fucked him, over and over and over. You lied to me!
三番兩次地 愛德華，拜託--
- Over and over and over. - Edward, please...
不，你不用馬上回答
No, you don't talk to me now.
我盡心盡力地付出...
I gave everything. . .
...為了這個家
. . .for this family.
費盡心血
Everything.
你又做了什麼？
And what did you do?
你像是毫無要緊地將它丟棄一旁
You threw it all away, like it was nothing.
為什麼？
For what?
為了那個該死的小孩
To the fucking kid.
你以為我不知道？
You didn't think I'd know?
我沒感覺到嗎？ 從第一天起我就曉得了
I wouldn't feel it? I knew it from the very first day.
因為我太瞭解你了，康妮 我瞭解你卻也該死的恨你
Because I know you, Connie. I know you and I fucking hate you.
我並不想殺他，我想殺的是你!
I didn't want to kill him, I wanted to kill you!
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
愛德華. 哦，天啊
Edward. Oh, my God.
天啊
Oh, my God.
媽，看我做的
Mom, look what I did.
甜心，不要緊. 不要緊的
Honey, it's okay. That's okay.
對不起，媽
I'm sorry, Mom.
只是意外，誰都難免有意外
It's an accident. Everybody has accidents.
你怎不回房睡，媽？
Why aren't you in bed, Mom?
我不知道
I don't know.
查理，看著我
Charlie, look at me.
我要你明白...
I want you to know. . .
...我愛你遠勝於世上任何一切
. . .that I love you, more than anything in the world.
我要你知道你爸和我兩個...
And I want you to know that your daddy and me both. . .
...會永遠永遠愛你
. . .will always, always love you.
無論如何
No matter what.
好嗎？ 好的
- Okay? - Okay.
好了，甜心
Come on, sweetie.
我們把你的床整理的乾乾淨淨，好嗎？
Let's go fix up your bed all nice and fresh, okay?
好的
All right.
你可以上來清洗一下傷口
You can come on up and clean it off, no?
來吧! 我不是什麼連環殺手，我發誓
Come on. I'm not an ax murderer. I promise.
出租車!
Taxi.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們要怎麼辦？
What are we going to do?
我好害怕
I'm so scared.
我去自首
I'll turn myself in.
不
No.
不，我們會大步攬過的
No, we can get through this.
我們一天一次，每次搬一點點
We'll take it one day at a time.
神不知鬼不覺的
No one will know.
而我們知道啊
We'll know.
3200，3500，3800，4000...
3200, 3500, 3800, 4000. . .
...42，45，4800!
. . .42, 45, 4800!
我們可以逃的無影無蹤
We can disappear.
可以籌一點錢
We can raise some money.
全都賣掉，然後離開這個國家
Sell everything and just leave the country.
小姐？
Senorita?
墨西哥
Mexico.
有何不可？
Why not?
我們可以買間靠海邊的小房子
We can get a little house on the beach.
用別的化名
Take a different name.
大家都是這樣子做
People do it all the time.
我們要怎麼告訴查理？
What will we tell Charlie?
告訴他這是一次冒險
Tell him it's an adventure.
我們可以整天釣魚
We could fish all day.
學學如何彈吉它
We could learn to play the guitar.
每晚對你唱小夜曲好讓你入睡
I would serenade you to sleep every night.
就在海邊度過餘生
We'll just live the rest of our lives on that beach.
等我們死了，就葬在海
And then when we die, we can just push out to sea.
你認為怎樣？
What do you think?
聽起來蠻不錯的
Sounds perfect.